stingervideos.com 2012-05-04

# Privacy Policy

StingerVideos.com is committed to customer service and strives to provide a private and secure browsing experience at our website. The following policy will help you to understand how we treat and use your personal information. As we continue to improve our site and services we may take advantage of developments in technology. When new technology is put in place, this policy is subject to change. 

**Information Collection and Use**

StingerVideos.com collects information from our web site in several ways including but not limited to, cookies and sessions. During registration, StingerVideos.com asks for some identifying information such as your email address. Because we are committed to protecting you privacy, StingerVideos.com will not sell or rent your personal information to any third party, unless you have provided prior permission for us to do so. When prior permission is provided, we will ensure that only your email address is utilised to update you about StingerVideos.com products and services via email. You may also be asked for personal information when you report a problem with our site and related services or, if you otherwise contact StingerVideos.com.

As previously stated StingerVideos.com collects information using cookies, which are small pieces of data stored by your browser and/or your computer's hard drive. This information allows us to more easily service your account needs and ensure proper tracking of sales in our affiliate referral program. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies unless specifically set not to, use of our website requires cookies.

StingerVideos.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site, however, we do not store any personal information other than what is necessary to provide proper service. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others for any reason. Information is collected with the sole purpose of providing StingerVideos.com services. 

When you are on the StingerVideos.com site only StingerVideos.com, its agents and representatives have access to your information. StingerVideos.com will not disclose any of your personal information except when we have your express permission or under special circumstances, such as when the law requires it. StingerVideos.com will comply with the requests of all recognized legal entities to aid in the stopping of spam, distribution of illicit sexual content to minors, or any other illegal activity brought to our attention through the proper legal channels.

StingerVideos.com may occasionally send you e-mail about promotions, service upgrades, and other information specifically pertaining to StingerVideos.com and the services we provide. Only StingerVideos.com (or agents or representatives working on behalf of StingerVideos.com) will send you these emails.

All movie/picture/sound files associated with your account are your property and StingerVideos.com has no authorization to use them in any way except as instructed by you in accordance with normal account operation. In the event that your account is cancelled for any reason we will delete any and all files in your account within thirty days of account cancellation.

Your movie/picture/sound files are stored in the same database as other account holders but are stored in such a way that they are kept separate from other account holders. At no time is information about your movie/picture/sound files shared with any other subscribers, affiliates or partners unless specifically requested by you or unless we must provide data in an effort to render a proper decision concerning spam complaints

This web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites unless they are specifically listed in this privacy policy. 

**END OF STINGERVIDEOS.COM PRIVACY POLICY**
